<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> Professional &amp; Personal Organizer  on Organized Vancouver</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Professional &amp; Personal Organizer  on Organized Vancouver</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 18:27:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Hire a Professional Organizer</title>
      <link>/blog/why-should-you-hire-a-professional-organizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 18:27:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why-should-you-hire-a-professional-organizer/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to organizing the spaces in your home, your office, or your documents, it can be hard to know where to start. Your home is your sanctuary and it is important that your spaces, your belongings and your processes work for you. Life has many stresses that are sometimes associated with change - moving home, changing relationships, changing jobs and having children. These changes present challenges - including a need to get organized or reorganize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I get on top of my schedule?</title>
      <link>/blog/how-do-i-get-on-top-of-my-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:34:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-do-i-get-on-top-of-my-schedule/</guid>
      <description>So many people struggle with time management despite the millions of blogs, books and magazines providing valuable advice on the topic. We all have cell phones with built in calendars and that doesn’t help everyone. Paper calendars remain an ever present option at the book store, the stationary store, the grocery store, the pharmacy, etc.
Clearly there is something to this. Life is very full. There is no shortage of ways we can spend our time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organized Travel</title>
      <link>/blog/organized-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 09:39:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/organized-travel/</guid>
      <description>Organized travel has its challenges. What to pack requires planning and some guess work. And one formula does not fit all trips.
Recently, I have been on a number of different business trips and they have all been so different. I have done several day trips by plane to various parts of BC. One day I may have to give a presentation. Another day might be a client meeting. I also had a recent week long business trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make the most of your wardrobe</title>
      <link>/blog/wardrobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 23:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/wardrobe/</guid>
      <description>Your master bedroom closet is more than just a place to store your clothing. It is the place from which all your amazing outfits are created.
There are many ways to organize your closet. Most often you would hear that tops should be together, bottoms together, jackets together. It makes sense - right? It is easier to choose an outfit when you know all the possible tops you can wear.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>